Talk Dirty
压制:随Feng
歌手：Jason Derulo feat. 2 Chainz
Jason
Jason Derulo
I'm that flight that you get on, international
妹子 哥高富帅 带你环游世界
First class seat on my lap girl, riding comfortable
哥的膝盖 就是你的头等舱 绝对舒适
Cause I know what the girl them need, New York to Haiti
妹子的心思哥最懂 纽约到海地畅通无阻
I got lipstick stamps on my passport, make it hard to leave
护照上唇印满布 想要离境也不容易
Been around the world, don't speak the language
曾环游世界 接触的语言不会讲
But your booty don't need explaining
但你的美体 不需语言诠释
All I really need to understand is
哥只想知道一件事
Will you talk dirty to me?
能对哥说下流话吗
Talk dirty to me
对哥开黄腔
对哥说荤段子
Talk dirty to me
对哥开黄腔
You know the words to my songs
你明白哥的歌词含义
No habla inglés
不要说英语
Our conversations ain't long
没有那么多对话
But you know what it is
但你知道那是什么意思
I know what the girl them want, London to Taiwan
哥明白女孩想要什么 伦敦到台湾 随手拈来
I got lipstick stamps on my passport
护照上满是唇印
I think I need a new one
是该换一个新的了
Been around the world, don't speak the language
曾环游世界 一堆语言不堪认识
But your booty don't need explaining
但你的美体不需诠释
All I really need to understand is
哥只想明白一件事
Will you talk dirty to me?
你会对哥说脏话吗
Talk dirty to me
对哥开黄腔
给哥说荤段子
Talk dirty to me
对哥开黄腔
Uno, met a friend in Rio
第一 在里约新泡了个妹子
Dos, she was all on me-o
第二 她对哥死心塌地
Tres, we could ménage à three-o
第三 哥们迅速短信联系
Dos Cadenas, clothes are genius
哥就是二链子 衣服最帅气
Sold out arenas, you can suck my penis
演唱会全场爆满 你们这些二货跪添去吧
Get with arenas, guns on deck
在体育场闪亮登场 枪早摆桌上
Chest to chest, tongue on neck
胸胸相撞 舌尖以至脖颈
International oral sex
大庭广众性感派对
Every picture I take, I pose a threat
拍下每张照片 哥都闪现出杀气
Boat or jet, what do you expect?
船或飞机 你想乘哪个
Her pussy so good I bought her a pet
木耳如此迷人 哥给她买个宠物
Anyway, every day I'm trying to get to it
每天哥都想爬上她的美体
Got her saved in my phone under "Big Booty"
把她的号码存进丰乳肥臀下
Anyway, every day I'm trying to get to it
每天哥都想爬上她的美体
Got her saved in my phone under "Big Booty"
把她的号码存进丰乳肥臀下
Been around the world, don't speak the language
曾环游世界 一堆语言不堪认识
But your booty don't need explaining
但你的美体不需诠释
All I really need to understand is
哥只想明白一件事
Will you talk dirty to me?
你会对哥说脏话吗
Talk dirty to me
对哥开黄腔
给哥说荤段子
Talk dirty to me
对哥开黄腔
What I don't understand
什么 我不明白你什么意思
压制:随Feng